Jessica Zackowitz

DevOps Engineer

Phone 410-279-0218

Portfolio www.jesszackowitz.com

E-mail jesszackowitz@gmail.com

Versatile DevOps manager with 6 years' experience. Seeking to leverage proven continuous deployment skills to raise quality at Google. Cut customer complaints by 50% for an SaaS application. At Shellnac Inc., used Jenkins and AWS tools to cut release times by 20%.

Boosted customer satisfaction by 25%.

Experience

2015-07 - 2018-08

DevOps Manager

Frostacre Global

- Led Agile team of 5 developers, 2 SysAdmins to continuous deployment of SaaS real estate solution with 1 million+ users. Collaborated with C-Suite and sales teams.
- Maintained network of 30+ Unix servers with 99.9% up-time.
- · Wrote scripts to automate security upgrades. Cut vulnerabilities by 20%.

2013-05 - 2015-06

DevOps Engineer

Shellnac Systems, Inc.

- · Set up and managed 40 Linux servers with 99.95% up-time.
- · Managed continuous deployment of a popular SaaS stock-tracking tool.
- Deployed 2 software iterations per month for 2 years. Increased customer satisfaction with software by 25%.
 Presided over a period of 30% revenue growth.

2012-06 - 2013-05

System Administrator

Litman Analytics

- · Set up and managed 15 Windows 2008 servers.
- · Wrote scripts to automatically update system components.
- · Cut company costs 20% through aggressive vendor management.

Education

2008 - 2012

BS in Computer Science, University of Michigan

- · Excelled in security classes.
- · President, 314 Action STEM Organization.

Soft Skills

Collaboration	••••
	Expert
Critical Thinking	••••
	Advanced

Hard Skills

Continuous Deployment	••••
, , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,	Expert
Unix/Linux	● ● ● ● Expert
Puppet, Jenkins, Zabbix	● ● ● ● Expert